http://www.arktimes.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
The Arkansas Times collects user information site-wide, including anonymous site statistics such as domain names and/or IP addresses. This information is used only in the aggregate, primarily to discover which features users are reading the most, what features they like best and what we can do to make things better. We may also share aggregate data with our advertisers.
Personal information
When you register on this website or use services on the site, we collect some personal information directly from you, typically just your e-mail address and zip code. If you register for a give-away or participate in a survey, we may also ask for your physical address, phone number, date of birth and/or gender. Such information is only gathered with users’ consent. We won’t provide your personal information to any third parties without your consent unless we are required to do so by law, court order or subpoena, or we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take actions regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of another person.
Targeted advertising
The Arkansas Times allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit networkadvertising.org.
Children
This website is not intended for children under 13. If that’s you, please leave. Neither the Arkansas Times nor any third party advertisers knowingly collect personal information on children under 13.
Public areas of the site
You should be aware that what you disclose in a publicly accessible part of the website could be collected and used by others. Anything that you reveal in a comment, review, on your profile page or any other publicly accessible place on this website, you do so at your own risk.
Links
We have no control or authority over the content or privacy policies of sites that are linked to on this site. Please understand that you follow links at your own risk.
How to contact us:
Arkansas Times
201 East Markham, Suite 200
P.O. Box 34010
Little Rock, AR 72203-4010
arktimes@arktimes.com
Changes to this policy
The Arkansas Times reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept those changes.
Advertisement
Subscribe
Supporting the Arkansas Times' independent journalism is more vital than ever. Help us deliver the latest daily reporting and analysis on news, politics, culture and food in Arkansas.
Subscribe
Newsletters
Events
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Read this month's issue
About the Times
Founded in 1974, the Arkansas Times is a lively, opinionated source for news, politics and culture in Arkansas. Our monthly magazine is distributed for free to over 500 locations in Central Arkansas.
History
Contact
Staff
Submit a tip
Customer support
Special Publications
Copyright ©2019, All rights reserved • Privacy Policy
